stargist.com 2015-02-15

# Iconway Media

  * [Home](http://iconwaymedia.com/) /
  * Privacy Policy 

### Effective May 2014

Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of the Internet sites, applications and services owned and operated by Iconway Media Limited including without limitation KokoFeed, Stargist, SugarSport and MobilePadi (collectively referred to as, “we,” “us” or “our”). 

Because the Internet is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, and held in other than the one in which you reside. By using our Services, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**1\. The Information We Collect Automatically**

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use the Services (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Services we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit.We will use such Usage Data to diagnose problems with our servers and software, to administer the Services, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party advertising networks and servers will also provide us reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked on the Services in a manner that does not identify personally any individual. 

**2\. The Information You Choose To Give Us**

You can visit the Services without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Personal Information”). We may collect additional information about you when you visit certain features of the Services or the pages of certain of our partners when you interact with offers and advertisements, when you contact us for support, when you log into the Services with your account, when you complete a survey, or when you enter promotions. 

**3\. Our Information Sharing Practices**

(a) Generally. Except as otherwise described in this section of our Privacy Policy, we will never share your Usage Data, Personal Information, Non-Personal Information, or Shared Information (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “User Information”) with any third party without your permission. 

(b) Advertisers. From time to time, we may share your Usage Data and Non-Personal Information to enable third parties who serve advertisements on the Services to deliver advertisements that will be relevant to you. We will not share any such information, however, in a manner that would enable the advertiser to personally identify you. 

(c) Aggregated Data. From time to time, we may share aggregated User Information with third parties. We will not share any aggregated data, however, in manner that would enable the recipient to personally identify you. 

(d) Other Disclosure Scenarios. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any User Information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Services’ infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (4) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy); and (5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity. 

**4\. Public Information.**

If you identify any User Information as public, you are authorizing us to share such information publicly. For example, you may elect to make certain Shared Information (such as your alias, bio, email or photos) publicly available. Also, there may be areas of the Services (e.g., message boards, discussion rooms, and other online forums) in which you are able to post information that will be available to all other users of the Services. By choosing to use these areas, you understand and agree that anyone may access, use, and disclose any information that you post to those areas. 

**5\. Cookies.**

We may set and access cookies on your computer. Upon your first visit to the Services, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer and stored on your hard drive when you visit a website. Many major Web services use cookies to provide useful features for their users. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We also may allow certain analytic services and providers of applications used on the Services (e.g., sharing buttons) to collect Non-Personally Identifiable information by placing cookies on the Services that will track certain performance of our Services, such as, web traffic, click-through, etc., in order to assist us and our service providers in better understanding the interests of our users and to better serve those interests. 

**6\. Advertising**

We may use other companies under agreements with us to serve advertisements when you visit and use the Services. These companies may collect and use click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over during your visits to the Services and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie, a third party web beacon and/or pixel tags to collect this information. None of them collect any personal information from your computer, such as your e-mail address. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to our cookies. 

**7\. Modifying and Deleting Your Personal Information.**

If you would like to modify or delete from our database any User Information you previously submitted to us, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. Please note that any User Information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your request, and that if you delete certain information you may not be able to order services in the future without re-submitting such information. Also, please note that we will maintain User Information in our database whenever we are required to do so by law. 

**8\. Security.**

We have implemented reasonable measures to help protect your User Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your User Information, we cannot entirely guarantee its security. 

**9\. Links.**

The Services may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other website and urge you to review such practices prior to submitting any information to such websites. 

**10\. Children’s Privacy.**

We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Services are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Services to children under the age of 13. 

**11\. Changes.**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If under any such update we make any material change to the way in which we treat your User Information, we will inform you of such change via email or by posting a notice on relevant areas of the Services. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date set forth therein. 

**12\. Questions.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@iconwaymedia.com.
